Mohd. Janisar

Chandigarh, India



in linkedin.com/in/mohd-janisar-705b921a8



mohdjanisar8604@gmail.com

Summary

I am a talented, ambitious and hardworking individual, with broad skills and experience in Full Stack Web Development, digital marketing, Video Editing, social media and leading projects.

Furthermore, I am adept at handling multiple tasks on a daily basis competently and at working well with politely.

A key strength is communication; building strong relationships with people in order to deliver the best results.

Experience



Freelance

Dec 2019 - Present (9 months +)



Taj Studio

Jan 2017 - Apr 2019 (2 years 4 months)

Event Planner

Crowne Plaza Muscat Oman Convention & Exhibition Centre

Mar 2016 - Apr 2019 (3 years 2 months)

Digital Marketing Consultant

Webyno

Jul 2017 - Feb 2018 (8 months)

Education

Chandigarh Group Of Colleges

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology 2019 - 2023

📘 Jawahar Lal Nehru Smarak Inter College

12th, Mathematics and Computer Science 2017 - 2019

Netaji Defense Academy

10th, Science 2015 - 2017

Licenses & Certifications

- Web Development Bootcamp Udemy: Online Courses
- MERN Stack Udemy: Online Courses

Python 3.6 - Udemy: Online Courses

SEO and Social Meadia Marketing Startegy - Skillshare

Adobe Illustrator CS6 - Udemy: Online Courses

Adobe dreamweaver CC 2020 - Udemy: Online Courses

Online Marketing Certified Associate (OMCA) - Udemy: Online Courses

Adobe audition CC 2020 - Udemy: Online Courses

Adobe Animate cc 202 - Udemy: Online Courses

Honors & Awards

Kapilvastu Mahatsav - District Magistrate

Dec 2018

This day celebrates as a festival in our district so there I was co-organizer. so in that time I had less experience but I got select for that position which was miracle for me but I learned a lot of things there

Skills

Web Development • Python (Programming Language) • MERN Stack • Engineering • Digital Marketing • Video Editing • Dreamweaver • Adobe Premiere Pro • Adobe Illustrator • Adobe Photoshop